{"questions": [{"question": "Which of the terms listed below refers to an example of crypto-malware?", "Ans1": "Backdoor", "Ans2": "Ransomware ", "Ans3": "Keylogger", "Ans4": "Rootkit ", "Correct": "1", "Rating": "11"}, {"question": "What does a VPN do?", "Ans1": "Bypass location restrictions", "Ans2": "Protects your traffic from people snooping on the network", "Ans3": "Provides some anonymity", "Ans4": "All of the above", "Correct": "3", "Rating": "11"}, {"question": "What does IDS stand for?", "Ans1": "Internet Denial Service", "Ans2": "Intrusion Detection System", "Ans3": "Internal Discussion System", "Ans4": "Instrusion Denial System", "Correct": "1", "Rating": "11"}, {"question": "Which of the terms listed below applies to a collection of intermediary comprised systems that are used as a platform for a DDoS attack?", "Ans1": "Honeynet", "Ans2": "Botnets", "Ans3": "Quarantine network", "Ans4": "Malware", "Correct": "1", "Rating": "11"}, {"question": "Malware that restrict access to files or the entire computer system until the user performs a requested action is called", "Ans1": "Adware", "Ans2": "Ransomware ", "Ans3": "Spyware", "Ans4": "Grayware", "Correct": "2", "Rating": "11"}, {"question": "Which of the following monitors and forwards user\u00e2\u20ac\u2122s activities and habits on the internet to someone else", "Ans1": "Malware", "Ans2": "Spyware", "Ans3": "Virus", "Ans4": "Adware", "Correct": "1", "Rating": "12"}, {"question": "When constructing a password you should: ", "Ans1": "Use your family member name, sports name, pet name and add a number on the end ", "Ans2": "Use phrases or misspelled words with embedded numbers and special characters ", "Ans3": "Use sequenced letters and numbers from your keyboard", "Ans4": "All of the above", "Correct": "1", "Rating": "12"}, {"question": "What is a threat to general users created by large collections of public data on the internet?", "Ans1": "Denial of service ", "Ans2": "Botnets", "Ans3": "Identity theft", "Ans4": "Phishing", "Correct": "2", "Rating": "12"}, {"question": "Which of the following is most secure", "Ans1": "Boat1234", "Ans2": "WhenTh!58Z", "Ans3": "into*48", "Ans4": "12345", "Correct": "1", "Rating": "12"}, {"question": "A standalone malicious computer program that automatically propagates over a network is called", "Ans1": "Trojan horse", "Ans2": "Worm", "Ans3": "Spam", "Ans4": "Ransomware", "Correct": "2", "Rating": "12"}, {"question": "What is \"Malware\"?", "Ans1": "A virus or worm", "Ans2": "A hacker tool", "Ans3": "A corrupted program", "Ans4": "Security software", "Correct": "1", "Rating": "13"}, {"question": "Which of the following allows a website to store information about a user on their computer", "Ans1": "Malware", "Ans2": "Phishing", "Ans3": "Cookies", "Ans4": "Adware", "Correct": "2", "Rating": "13"}, {"question": "Which of these is regularly used for secure online communication?", "Ans1": "Caesar cipher", "Ans2": "Public-key cryptography", "Ans3": "Morse code", "Ans4": "Enigma code", "Correct": "1", "Rating": "13"}, {"question": "A command-line utility used for checking the reachability of a remote network host is called:", "Ans1": "ping", "Ans2": "tracert", "Ans3": "dig", "Ans4": "netstat", "Correct": "0", "Rating": "14"}, {"question": "A network security access control method whereby the 48-bit physical address assigned to each network cart is used to determine access to the network is known as:", "Ans1": "MAC filtering", "Ans2": "Netowrk Address Translation", "Ans3": "Static IP addressing", "Ans4": "Network Access Control", "Correct": "0", "Rating": "15"}]}